我们会分析消灭行动目标的
We take into account the strategic value
战略价值
of eliminating a target,
以及潜在的对平民
the potential damage to civilians,
领近的寺院  学校  医院的附带损害
and the proximity to mosques, schools, or hospitals.
这些数据会全部输入电脑进行计算
This is all entered into a computer algorithm,
再据此确定是否进行攻击
which determines the worthiness of an attack.
所以有一部分的平民伤亡
So there are some deaths of civilians
是被允许的
that are deemed appropriate.
遗憾地说是这样  有时候杀死基地组织
Unfortunately, yes, sometimes the value of killing
目标比少许平民伤亡更重要
an al-Qaeda target outweighs killing civilians.
在打击基地组织成员
That was the case
达萨里的时候就是这种情况吗
with the al-Qaeda operative, Amad al Dasari?
被告辩称这些行动中也存在平民伤亡
The defense has argued that someone should have been arrested
于是也应该有人对此承担责任
in that attack because civilians were killed.
不是这样的  那些行动是被批准的
No, that attack was sanctioned.